Contact

sandy.lenarz@granditasca.or

www.linkedin.com/in/sandy-lenarz-mha-bsn-59121156 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Education
Pediatrics
Patient Education

Sandy Lenarz, MHA, BSN

CNO and Vice President of Hospital Services at Grand Itasca Clinic and Hospital

Grand Rapids, Minnesota

Summary

Experienced Nursing Executive with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Disease Management, Clinical Research, Nursing Education, Community Health, and Quality. Exceptional communication and team building skills, a strong healthcare professional.

Experience

Grand Itasca Clinic & Hospital 9 years 6 months

Vice President Hospital Services September 2016 - Present (3 years 11 months) Grand Rapids, Minnesota

Director Nursing MedSurg/Homecare February 2011 - Present (9 years 6 months)

Presbyterian Homes and Services
Director Of Nursing
April 2005 - January 2011 (5 years 10 months)
Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

Minneapolis University of Minnesota Fairview May 1992 - March 2005 (12 years 11 months)

Education

University of Minnesota-Twin Cities

Executive Masters Healthcare Administration · (2014 - 2016)

Bethel University

Bachelor's degree, Nursing Science

College of St. Catherine Associate's degree, Nursing